All right, coach. How did this compare
to other pro days that you've been to
and what made it so different? Well,
it's a little different when your son's
in it, obviously.
So, you know, it's obviously a great
opportunity to get out and evaluate, you
know, all the great LSU players here,
but obviously special for us and our
family and like I've said many times,
blessed. Is this Did this day come with
maybe a little bit more nerves than
usual for pro day? Oh, definitely. Of
course.
Listen, I don't know if there's nerves.
I know how hard Garrett and and his
teammates had prepared for this day.
These guys work extremely hard for these
opportunities, all these boys. And so,
you know, just to get the opportunity to
get out here and watch them in person is
great. How do you think he did?
I think he did fine. Yeah? I think he
actually had a pretty good workout. You
know what I mean? I think they the whole
group, the guys ran well, caught well. I
thought it was a really clean workout.
High-level execution on some stuff from
all of them. Like what What's it like?
I'm sure you knew a little more than
everyone in the public knew about what
he was dealing with during the season.
How hard is that to to watch him go
through that and and I mean, are you
proud? Are you frustrated as a dad?
>> You know, that that's football. That's
football. And
you know, I don't think you were going
to tell a fifth-year senior who had
waited his turn here at LSU and and this
place means so much to him and this
state he was going to play with whatever
he had until he just couldn't go
anymore, you know? And that's the
reality of it, but proud of the way he
fought, proud of the way their team
fought. Obviously, it wasn't the year
anybody had hoped for, but that's the
way it goes. And then is this this part
of the process when you're doing draft
evaluations, is it really important in
cases like that where you get to kind of
see him in his best now? Yeah, I think,
you know, you look back at
you know, every player we look at, you
know, we have to evaluate the
circumstances. So, you know, Garrett was
fortunate enough to play in 2024, so you
have tape to go back to watch a 24 to
see a healthy player and now, okay, you
watch the tape 25, you see the injury
and then you get to see this. You you're
talking about the Senior Bowl,
you talk about going to the combine,
you're talking about pro days. We do
that with every player and every
position because you're always trying to
find out, you know, where is the player,
where are they going, you know, where at
what level are they at right now, what
level can we take them to.
You obviously
watching us, you know a lot about his
weapons as well as Zion Thomas is a guy
who LSU used in a lot of different ways.
What did you like about maybe what you
saw from him in his workouts and how can
he translate to the NFL?
>> Like I said, I thought it was a really
good workout for all the boys.
You know,
that's a great group of skill guys out
there, right? And you watch them
the transition, their their speed, their
burst, their energy, their ability to
track the ball. You know, I thought they
all had wonderful workouts. I mean, you
looked at the the workout, there wasn't
any balls on the ground. Was there two
balls on the ground I think the whole
day? So, that speaks to everybody, not
just the quarterback. You're talking
about route detail. You know, you watch
guys getting out of breaks, tracking the
ball. Like I said, I thought it was a
really really clean, good workout.
When your son is dealing with an injury
like you said, like as a dad, do you
feel compelled to give him advice
knowing exactly what the position
entails or are you kind of person who
just lets him
>> No, Garrett was coached Garrett was
coached by phenomenal coaches here.
You know, phenomenal training staff and
doctors. So, you know, when you go
through these things, you go through
them and
it's not my job to coach my son.
Joe Sloan and Brian Kelly did an
outstanding job coaching Garrett. Are
you allowed to give honest evaluations
to other teams or do they not bother
calling you because of a conflict or
[laughter]
Oh, there's no conflict of interest, is
there? No, I
listen, it's a unique situation. I don't
know. It's
I guess I go back to what my best friend
told me about parenting, you know, just
remember they don't know, you don't
know. So,
it's kind of a
I've never been in this situation. I
don't know what how it's going to go,
how, you know, so you just kind of go
through the process. You know, obviously
we have background in what the process
is and that type of stuff, but
to have somebody, you know, your own son
going through it, like I said, um
you got to feel blessed and at same
time, you just, you know, pulling for
them to do their best. Have to that
point, have anyone reached out to Have
other teams reached out to you about us?
Well, you have, you know, friends in in
the league and people talk and, you
know, obviously there's been a lot of
questions about the injury and and what
it was and those type of things. So,
you know, there's people you talk to all
the time,
Seth used to call him Nuss, so you
aren't you Nuss
>> [laughter]
>> or is he Nuss? Well, I tell all I tell
both the boys, there's only a real one
real 13 in the household and they know
who it is.
>> [laughter]
>> Often imitated, never duplicated, okay?
No, I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding.
They're both way better players than I
ever was, so.
How about like the Saints have done in
free agency, especially
bolstering the offensive line, running
back, run game? Really excited about our
football team. Excited about the way we
finished the season. Obviously, we've
got a tremendous amount of work to do,
but you know, to add David, to add
Travis, to add Noah,
and you know, we'll continue to look at
our roster and look at ways to improve
and just like, you know, as coaches
right now, we're spending half of our
days in the meeting room evaluating what
we're doing offensively,
which has been refreshing um just from
being on the move for the last couple
years, you're really coming into a place
to teach a system
and really not have enough time to go
back and really deep dive into the
system. So, having the opportunity that
to make the changes that we're going to
make to help make us a better football
team.
You know, we spend half our day doing
that and then we spend the other half of
the day evaluating the draft. And just
having that fans, you guys have been
recruiting him for quite a while now.
Yeah, I guess we just had to twist his
arm a little harder.
I mean, just you kind of mentioned it
there, but just having pretty much the
whole staff other than Jaray back and
just being able to kind of build year
over year, how valuable is that? Well, I
think it it speaks volumes to the
organization.
You know, starts at the top, obviously
with Ms. Benson and then, you know, with
Mickey and and and then down to Kellen.
Um When you have guys have opportunities
to go to other places and they choose to
stay, that tells you something.
And you mentioned Travis in in signing
him at running back.
He's a guy that we've been able to see a
lot from being a local guy, playing at
Clemson, right? How much can his speed
add to what you want to do on Jennings,
Louisiana, you know, the southwest side
of the state.
Um
you know, obviously Travis is a
phenomenal football player. Had a
tremendous year this year.
I've followed him for a long time.
So, really excited about what he brings
to our offense.
He's a juice guy. Obviously, his you
know, his resume speaks for itself.
Really excited. And several of the guys
mentioned Shuck, the way that he played
late in the season and just that
influence of, "Hey, I want to be a part
of that." What do you think that that
says and how much can he he grow? Oh,
Tyler's got a ton of growth. We're just
starting to scratch the surface and
you know, I'll say this about him, his
work ethic, his dedication, his want to
is unreal and and his work ethic, he's
in all the time.
He always wants to get better and he's a
really smart guy that is looking for the
next step.
Real quick, what are some attributes of
Garrett that you see that could
translate to the NFL? Just I don't know
from your perspective. Um you know, I
think you know, he's got good he's got
quick feet. He can get back get to the
set point and the ball comes out, he can
anticipate and he's got his accuracy.
So, when you got those components, you
got a pretty good chance. As a parent,
what would be the ideal landing spot for
Garrett in the draft? Oh, you're going
to put me on the spot on that?
One of the NFL teams, how about that?
>> [laughter]